Friends, in this video I am going to
show you how
and when the No Due Certificate from AAA Bank comes. I had
purchased a phone on my debit card. You
can still watch that video if you want. I will provide the
link in the description. Its
thumbnail is something like this. I had
purchased it 6 months ago there. You can
see it through the mobile debit card. This is
my iMobile Pay app. Whether you
take any EMI or loan on your debit card, you
purchase it and make the payment. The full payment gets
exhausted. Or if you
take it on a credit card and pay the full EMI, it gets
exhausted. So you do
n't need to search for the No Due Certificate. It automatically
comes to your email ID. So let me
explain it to you in detail. First of all, you can see it.
This is my iMobile Pay app. First, I will
show you the statement. The EMI is deducted.
After that, I will also show you the NOC. So, I quickly
click on the detail statement
and I select my date from
when I am paying my EMI. Let
me directly select six months here.  It will be
visible in that also,
okay, so you can see here that
my EMI has been deducted which is written as Consumer Loan on
3rd June 2024, 83 is at the end,
5826, 5826, okay, this is how it has been deducted
and after that 9 more were deducted, similarly you
can see here also that on 3rd July this much
amount has been deducted, similarly
it used to deduct my EMI on 3rd of every month,
I will again show it on 3rd of the next month, you
can see here that on
3rd August this much amount has been deducted as
Consumer Loan and at the end 5826 and here
also it has been deducted in September also, okay,
similarly it has been deducted in October also, so what
I mean to say is that my total EMI is over
and I will show you the No Due
Certificate, so my
Gmail is 26 and here I have attached a PDF
below and its
password is mentioned here,
how to open its password, if your name is Sujit then
you should have Suji and your birthday  You have to
enter the date and month, okay,
put it in small letters not in capital letters, so I will
enter mine, like my name
is Vishal and this is a loan in my name, so I will
enter V I S and H,
I have put the first four letters of my name here, now
I will enter the date of my birthday,
after that I will enter the date, I have entered the month, I have entered the month, let me
open it, you can see here that
mine has opened, so here
my no due certificate has opened, I will
zoom it and show you, here
my name and my address are written, you
can see below that here dear customer,
my loan number is visible here
₹1500000, after that the no due certificate will
come to your email ID, if you have taken a loan online,
whether it is from a credit card
or a debit card, I have
taken loans from many credit cards as well
and their no due certificate is also
kept on my email, it is from ADAC, it is
also from Kotak, so I hope you have
understood how you will get the no due certificate of III Bank
Video
Thanks for watching